Why did you buy so many pineapple cakes?
To use as bait.
Guess.
What is it for?
What took you so long?
We got delayed by something.
How is it?
Did you spot him?
Not yet.
How do you know
Qian Yanqing will show up here?
Accurate intel from my informant.
Qian Yanqing bought a ticket to Dagu yesterday.
His hometown is Dagu.
That intersection.
It's the only way to the station.
Mr. Qian!
Don't run!
Screw you!
Pick it up later.
Flank him.
Go.
Don't come any closer!
Don't push me!
If you push me,
we'll die together!
Mr. Qian,
if you confess everything,
I'll plead for you
for leniency.
Are you kidding me?
What I've done,
I know exactly.
I'll say it again.
Let me go,
or else
we'll die together!
Mr. Qian,
you don't have to take the blame for everything.
What's the point of taking the fall alone?
What good does it do you, right?
Put down the grenade.
I'll help you.
Detective Jiang,
you have no idea
who you're up against,
what kind of big shot they are.
No matter who they are,
if they break the law, they will be arrested.
All of them.
Try and catch me.
Watch out.
Are you okay?
Don't move.
How is it?
Keep running.
I told you not to run.
Why are you so strong?
Stand still.
Take him away.
Qian Yanqing.
As for your crimes and the Jingxiang Society,
we have already investigated them thoroughly.
I only have one question for you now.
Who is the Master?
I don't know who he is either.
Describe his physical appearance.
He is of medium build,
quite thin,
and has a loud voice.
Oh, right.
On his right arm,
he seems to have cigarette burns.
Three of them,
about the size of a fingernail.
Where exactly?
Here.
Jinwen,
how did you get these three scars?
I've asked you several times before, but you never told me.
This?
I was naughty when I was a kid.
I got poked by a branch.
It's ancient history.
Hurry up and eat,
or it'll get cold.
Come on, eat more.
It doesn't look like a poke.
Master
gives a lecture on the 15th of every month.
He didn't come last month,
and up until now,
he hasn't shown up.
You guys interrogate him first.
I'm going out for a cup of tea.
Qian Yanqing, go on.
Is there anything else different?
What are you dawdling for?
Besides wearing a mask,
is there anything else special?
He only appears on the 15th of every month
to preach at the base.
Preaches on the 15th of every month.
Jinwen.
Do you want to spend the Mid-Autumn Festival at my house?
No, I have a mission.
Wait.
I noticed that not only on the Mid-Autumn Festival,
but you also go out on missions on the 15th of every month.
Why? Are you going to turn into a monster?
Even if I turn into a monster,
I'll snatch you away first.
Siyao.
What are you looking at?
Who let you in?
Why didn't you knock?
I've been knocking for a long time.
What's wrong?
I need to know
Lin Jinwen's recent attendance records.
Go find them for me.
Why are you suddenly looking at this?
Don't ask what you shouldn't.
Okay.
Don't forget
to take the things I bought for you back with you.
What things?
I bought you so much.
You mean
those pineapple cakes
were for me?
What's this for?
Ningning told me everything.
It was you who insisted on rushing to
the Jingxiang Society's headquarters to save me.
Alright.
For you.
Hey you,
where is Detective Jiang?
Who are you calling 'hey you'?
Miss Huo,
where is Detective Jiang?
He didn't come.
What?
Does our Detective Jiang need to
ask you for leave?
That won't be necessary.
Detective Jiang has been working too hard lately.
He needs a good day of rest.
Even draft animals need a good rest.
That makes sense.
Looks like we don't need to investigate today.
Stop right there.
Am I invisible?
Let me tell you.
As long as I'm here,
there's no case I can't solve.
Where are you going?
It's noon.
I'm hungry.
You're buying me lunch.
I'll treat you.
Who treats a girl to just steamed buns?
Boss,
give him two more baskets of steamed buns.
Let him eat to death.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Eat.
Stop messing around.
Let me ask you,
don't you think Detective Jiang
was a bit unusual yesterday?
How dare you talk about my senior sister?
I'm talking about serious business.
Spit it out.
Yesterday,
when Qian Yanqing mentioned the Master,
she looked distracted,
and then went out.
So what?
Are you going to keep farting
one by one?
What I mean is,
no, I mean what if
Detective Jiang
and the Master
actually knew each other a long time ago,
and they have a secret relationship?
A mouse eating arsenic.
I think you have a death wish.
Okay.
Then what's your brilliant idea, Officer Huo?
Then let me give you some pointers.
What's this?
Qian Yanqing said
this was given by the Master
to the senior members of the Jingxiang Society.
Look at the pattern on it.
Can you see anything?
No.
Seed embroidery.
I've seen this since I was a kid.
Normal seed embroidery
uses double threads
wrapped around once to make a seed.
This one uses a single thread
wrapped around twice to make a seed.
And the embroidery thread shines with gold.
This uses...
Really?
Go on.
There is only one place in the whole city
that uses this embroidery method and thread to make sachets.
Furui Embroidery Shop.
Boss.
You two,
what do you need?
Boss,
take a look.
Was this sachet
custom-made here?
Xiao Lin did it.
Who ordered it?
Who?
I have some impression.
But,
I don't know his name.
What did he look like?
Do you still remember?
About average height.
Right.
I remember.
Although he was wearing a long gown,
the leather shoes he wore
were the kind only police officers can wear,
standard Meihua leather shoes.
This is the chief of Linjia Village.
Greetings, Officer.
If you need anything from me,
I will tell you everything I know.
Don't be nervous, Chief.
I just want to ask you about someone.
His name is Lin Jinwen,
from Linjia Village.
Lin Jinwen?
Everyone in our village is surnamed Lin.
I really don't remember this name.
He is 28 years old this year.
He left to become a soldier a long time ago.
Officer, it's like this.
Those warlords
come to our village every now and then to conscript men.
Many people from our village became soldiers.
I really don't remember this name.
Thank you, Chief.
You're welcome.
It seems I still know too little about him.
I only know he is from Linjia Village.
Don't lose heart.
Isn't there another clue?
You mean...
The army.
I've already sent someone to contact Commander Liu.
He should be here soon.
Commander Liu has arrived!
Commander Liu,
please have a seat.
Hello, Commander Liu.
I am Jiang Siyao.
You have quite a reputation.
Not as famous as Commander Liu.
Speak.
What do you want from me?
I want to ask you about someone.
Ten years ago,
you had a soldier under your command
named Lin Jinwen.
Lin Jinwen.
He used to be a squad leader under my command.
Ten years ago,
when we were fighting the Queue Army.
He died in battle.
Yes.
His parents died early.
He had been with me since he was a teenager.
I originally planned
for him to transfer to be a police officer later.
What a pity.
Commander Liu,
is this the person?
This person is not Lin Jinwen.
Let me think.
His name is
Lin Yousheng.
Right.
I was still a company commander back then.
He came to me to join the army.
I didn't want him because he was too young.
But seeing he was homeless,
I took pity on him
and let him follow Lin Jinwen.
But after Lin Jinwen died in battle,
no one knows where he went.
Lin Yousheng.
His name is actually Lin Yousheng.